<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Core-values on Matilda L. Bradford Christian School, Inc.</title>
    <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Core-values on Matilda L. Bradford Christian School, Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:44 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 1</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-1/</guid>
      <description>Imagine Dragon - Bones Gimme, gimme, gimme some time to think I&amp;rsquo;m in the bathroom, looking at me Face in the mirror is all I need (ooh) Wait until the reaper takes my life Never gonna get me out alive I will live a thousand million lives (ooh)
My patience is waning Is this entertaining? Our patience is waning Is this entertaining?
I-I-I got this feeling, yeah, you know Where I&amp;rsquo;m losing all control &amp;lsquo;Cause there&amp;rsquo;s magic in my bones I-I-I got this feeling in my soul Go ahead and throw your stones &amp;lsquo;Cause there&amp;rsquo;s magic in my bones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 2</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:41 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-2/</guid>
      <description>Oh, hush, my dear, it&amp;rsquo;s been a difficult year And terrors don&amp;rsquo;t prey on Innocent victims Trust me, darling, trust me, darling It&amp;rsquo;s been a loveless year I&amp;rsquo;m a man of three fears Integrity, faith and Crocodile tears Trust me, darling, trust me, darling
So look me in the eyes Tell me what you see Perfect paradise Tearing at the seams I wish I could escape I don&amp;rsquo;t wanna fake it Wish I could erase it Make your heart believe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 3</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-3/</guid>
      <description>Just a young gun with a quick fuse I was uptight, wanna let loose I was dreaming of bigger things And wanna leave my old life behind Not a yes-sir, not a follower Fit the box, fit the mold Have a seat in the foyer, take a number I was lightning before the thunder
Thunder, thunder Thunder, thun-, thunder Thun-thun-thunder, thunder, thunder Thunder, thun-, thunder Thun-thun-thunder, thunder
Thunder, feel the thunder Lightning then the thunder Thunder, feel the thunder Lightning then the thunder Thunder, thunder Thunder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 4</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:34 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-4/</guid>
      <description>I used to rule the world Seas would rise when I gave the word Now in the morning, I sleep alone Sweep the streets I used to own
I used to roll the dice Feel the fear in my enemy&amp;rsquo;s eyes Listen as the crowd would sing Now the old king is dead, long live the king One minute, I held the key Next the walls were closed on me And I discovered that my castles stand Upon pillars of salt and pillars of sand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 5</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-5/</guid>
      <description>Look at the stars Look how they shine for you And everything you do Yeah, they were all yellow
I came along I wrote a song for you And all the things you do And it was called Yellow
So then I took my turn Oh, what a thing to have done And it was all yellow
Your skin, oh yeah, your skin and bones Turn into something beautiful And you know, you know I love you so You know I love you so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 6</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:27 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-6/</guid>
      <description>25 years and my life is still Tryin&amp;rsquo; to get up that great big hill of hope For a destination I realized quickly when I knew I should That the world was made up of this brotherhood of man For whatever that means
And so I cry sometimes when I&amp;rsquo;m lying in bed Just to get it all out what&amp;rsquo;s in my head And I, I am feeling a little peculiar And so I wake in the morning and I step outside And I take a deep breath and I get real high And I scream from the top of my lungs &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s going on?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Value 7</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:24:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/core-values/core-value-7/</guid>
      <description>I know they don&amp;rsquo;t like me that much Guess that I don&amp;rsquo;t dress how they want I just wanna be myself, I can&amp;rsquo;t be someone else Try to colour inside their lines Try to live a life by design I just wanna be myself, I can&amp;rsquo;t be someone else Someone else
They yell, they preach I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it all before Be this, be that I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it before Heard it before</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
