<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Safety-security-faqs on Matilda L. Bradford Christian School, Inc.</title>
    <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Safety-security-faqs on Matilda L. Bradford Christian School, Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:01:08 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. How do we apply for a student ID?</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:01:08 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-1/</guid>
      <description>Applications must be done online following this link: https://forms.office.com/r/K9wWpqwYxM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3. How do we inquire about carpool service providers? </title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:01:04 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-3/</guid>
      <description>Please give us a call through 3454378 loc 1134 and we will be happy to provide some information and answer your questions regarding our serviced routes and carpool service providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. Can parents stay inside the campus?</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:01:02 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-4/</guid>
      <description>Nullam at urna nisi. Curabitur luctus et eros ac egestas. Aliquam maximus imperdiet felis, eu egestas ex faucibus vel. Aliquam eleifend nunc ac bibendum tristique. In rutrum porta faucibus. Donec eget mi est. Sed et sapien in dui sollicitudin varius. Quisque eu ullamcorper sapien. Mauris mauris quam, hendrerit et varius malesuada, egestas sit amet sapien. Etiam a lectus vel diam bibendum pretium ultrices quis justo. Phasellus eu elementum velit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5. What is the standard protocol once someone is Covid positive? Is proof of vaccination compulsory?</title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:54 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-5/</guid>
      <description>When someone becomes Covid positive, the medical team will identify the close contacts and determine based on proximity and circumstances if they are low risk, medium risk or high risk. The Covid positive is prohibited from entering the campus. He/she has to finish the isolation period before he/she can be allowed to come back to school with clearance from the school physician. Proof of vaccination is needed by the medical team to help us determine period of isolation and quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6. How do we ensure that our students are safe? </title>
      <link>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:51 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://preview.matildabradford.com/safety-security-faqs/faqs-6/</guid>
      <description>We have established health and safety protocols which are being practiced by all members of the school community, even guests and visitors who come to the campus to transact official business.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
